好了 尝一口吧
Okay. Take a sip.
你肯定猜不出饮料里混了什么
You will never guess what's in this one.
脱脂奶  鳄梨汁  花生酱  一丁点青春痘痂
Skim milk, avocado, peanut butter, a hint of zit puss,
芹菜汁和半个嚼烂的鸡块
celery juice and half a chewed-up chicken nugget.
尽管我说过了  但我还是要赞叹一遍
I have said it before, and I will say it again.
太惊人了
Amazing.
小伙子们  小伙子们
Boys boys boys boys boys boys.
准备好欢欣鼓舞吧
Set your phasers to excitement.
好的
Okay.
《太空狼人》的制片人刚刚来电话了
The producers of "space werewolves" just called.
很显然主演的候选名单上还剩下三个人了
There are apparently only three actors still in the running for the lead,
而我就是其中之一
and I'm one of them!
哇
Whoo!
《太空狼人》
"Space werewolves"
是有史以来最伟大的科幻漫画小说了
is the greatest Sci-Fi graphic novel ever.
这是半人半狼的特里斯坦·莱肯和他的
It is the epic tale of Tristan Lycanth, half-wolf, half-human,
星球保卫战的史诗故事
and his battle to save his planet.
就像是《星球大战》和《指环王》的生了个孩子
It is like "star wars" and "lord of t rings" had a baby,
又被了《复仇者联盟》领养长大一样
and then "the avengers" adopted it.
特里斯坦是全宇宙最坏的家伙了
Tristan is the baddest dude in the galaxy.
但是丽芙要出演 编剧就要把角色的性别从男改女
But if Liv gets the part, they're gonna change him to a her.
这样全宇宙最坏的家伙
And then the baddest dude in the galaxy
就成了
will be...
我姐姐
My sister.
伙计们 我最后一次试镜就在这周
Guys, my final audition is in a week.
这个角色也许会让我在电影界一举成名
This is the part that could make me a movie star.
难以置信
Unbelievable.
我姐姐就要成为特里斯坦·莱肯了
My sister is gonna be Tristan Lycanth.
和你竞争的那俩倒霉蛋是谁啊
Who are the two losers you're up against?
莱恩·戈斯林和范·迪塞尔
Ryan Gosling and Vin Diesel.
（莱恩·戈斯林 《恋恋笔记本》主演；范·迪塞尔 《拯救大兵瑞恩》主演）
噢
Ohh!